<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-26T21:29:25+01:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gnomengineer</title><subtitle>A small website displaying my experience and projects done as a software engineer</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to … well… here, I guess!</title><link href="/welcome-to-jekyll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to ... well... here, I guess!" /><published>2020-03-23T13:19:24+01:00</published><updated>2020-03-23T13:19:24+01:00</updated><id>/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/welcome-to-jekyll/">&lt;p&gt;Hello&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You seem to have stumbled upon this blog / project portfolio / self-promotion
of me, the &lt;em&gt;gnomengineer&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
I started using this alias a while back and it still fits me to this day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My real name is Daniel and I’m an engineer in real as well.
I finished my study as &lt;em&gt;Software Engineer&lt;/em&gt; 2018 and work now for already aa couple of years in this field.&lt;br /&gt;
As I begin to gather more knowledge I want to share this with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Knowledge has a Beginning but no End&lt;br /&gt;
— random internet quote&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even thou my work experience is relatively low I already encountered a lot of situations and learned already a lot of stuff.
With that and all the information and technology the future brings, I started this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From time to time I will blog a bit.
These blog posts will be a kind of a &lt;em&gt;how-to&lt;/em&gt; on the topic they cover.
Keep in mind that these posts are not a set way and should rather be used as guidelines through your work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess that’s as close as I can explain it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the project side I will include ongoing or finished projects which are worth sharing.
With &lt;em&gt;worth sharing&lt;/em&gt; I mean they follow a plan and can give the developer or user more concrete information about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, I hope you can get some value out of here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— sincerely, &lt;em&gt;gnomengineer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello You seem to have stumbled upon this blog / project portfolio / self-promotion of me, the gnomengineer. I started using this alias a while back and it still fits me to this day. My real name is Daniel and I’m an engineer in real as well. I finished my study as Software Engineer 2018 and work now for already aa couple of years in this field. As I begin to gather more knowledge I want to share this with you. Knowledge has a Beginning but no End — random internet quote Even thou my work experience is relatively low I already encountered a lot of situations and learned already a lot of stuff. With that and all the information and technology the future brings, I started this website. From time to time I will blog a bit. These blog posts will be a kind of a how-to on the topic they cover. Keep in mind that these posts are not a set way and should rather be used as guidelines through your work. I guess that’s as close as I can explain it. On the project side I will include ongoing or finished projects which are worth sharing. With worth sharing I mean they follow a plan and can give the developer or user more concrete information about them. All in all, I hope you can get some value out of here. — sincerely, gnomengineer</summary></entry></feed>